angular.module('friendsJeopardyApp')
  .controller('FriendsIndexController', FriendsIndexController);

FriendsIndexController.$inject = ['$uibModal', '$scope', 'TurnTrackerService'];
function FriendsIndexController(   $uibModal,  $scope,  TurnTrackerService) {
  var vm = this;
  vm.teams= TurnTrackerService.teams;
  vm.currentTeam = TurnTrackerService.currentTeam;
  vm.disabled = false;
  var count  = 0;
  vm.winner = {};
  console.log("HERE",TurnTrackerService.teams);
//WELCOME MODAL:
var welcomeInstance = $uibModal.open({
  animation: true,
  templateUrl: 'templates/modalWelcome.html',
  controller: 'ModalWelcomeCtrl',
  controllerAs: 'welcomeCtrl',
  backdrop: 'static',
  windowClass: "modal-welcome",
  keyboard: false,
  size: "sm"
});

welcomeInstance.result.then(function (teams){
  TurnTrackerService.currentTeam = teams[0];
  TurnTrackerService.teams = teams;

  vm.teams = teams;
  vm.currentTeam = teams[0];

}, function (){
  console.log('WELCOME MODAL DISMISSED AT:' + new Date());

});

//VM IS WATCHING
$scope.$watch(
  function(){ return { currentTeam: TurnTrackerService.currentTeam, teams: TurnTrackerService.teams, winner: TurnTrackerService.winningTeam }}, function (newVal, oldVal) {
  if (typeof newVal !== 'undefined') {
    console.log("OLD VALUE", oldVal);
    console.log("NEW VALUE", newVal);
      vm.currentTeam = TurnTrackerService.currentTeam;
      vm.teams = TurnTrackerService.teams;

      if ( JSON.stringify(newVal.winner) !== JSON.stringify({}) ) {
        vm.winner = newVal.winner;

        var winningModal = $uibModal.open({
          animation: true,
          templateUrl: 'templates/modalWinner.html',
          controller: 'ModalWinnerCtrl',
          controllerAs: 'winnerCtrl',
          backdrop: 'static',
          windowClass: "modal-winner",
            keyboard: false,
          resolve: {
            winner: vm.winner
          }
        });
      }//END OF NEW VAL IF STATEMENT
  }
}, true);



// MODAL OPENING:
  vm.hello = function (e, card) {
  var modalInstance = $uibModal.open({
    animation: true,
    templateUrl: 'templates/modalContent.html',
    controller: 'ModalInstanceCtrl',
    controllerAs: 'modalCtrl',
    backdrop: 'static',
    windowClass: 'modal-aq',
    keyboard: false,
    resolve: {
      card: function () {
        return card;
      }
    }
  });

  modalInstance.result.then(function (card) {
    vm.card = card;
  }, function () {
    console.log('Modal dismissed at: ' + new Date());
  });
};




///QUESTIONS
  vm.questionsRelationships = [
	{
		question:"Who was the last to know about Chandler and Monica?",
		answer: "Ross",
		score: 100,
		catagory: "Relationships",
		count: 30,
		vidanswer:"<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/al4PcS2tzjU?start=69&end=119' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>",
	},

	{
		question:"What nationality is Rachel's boyfriend Paolo?",
		answer: "Italian",
		score: 200,
		catagory: "Relationships",
		count: 30,
	},

	{
		question:"Besides Rachel, who is the women that both Ross and Joey dated?",
		answer: "Charlie",
		score: 300,
		catagory: "Relationships",
		count: 30,
	},

	{
		question:"What does the shirt say?",
		answer: "Frankie Say Relax",
		score: 400,
		catagory: "Relationships",
		count: 80,
		vid: "<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/qrrYZ9m6DFM?start=80&end=127' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>",
		vidanswer: "<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/qrrYZ9m6DFM?start=126&end=155' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>"

	},

	{
		question:"Why was Chandler in a box?",
		answer: "He kissed Kathy.",
		score: 500,
		catagory: "Relationships",
		count: 30,
		vidanswer:"<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/arlawWou2BU?start=1&end=23' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>"
	}
];

vm.questionsPinnacleEvents = [
  {
		question:"As Ross was moving into his new apartment, who were the other two friends that was helping him move the couch?",
		answer: "Chandler and Rachel",
		score: 100,
		catagory: "Pinnacle Events",
		count: 30,
		vidanswer:"<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/n67RYI_0sc0?start=0' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>",
	},

	{
		question:"Who was the last of the Friends group to turn 30?",
		answer: "Rachel",
		score: 200,
		catagory: "Pinnacle Events",
		count: 30,
	},

	{
		question:"Why was Ross called 'Mental' at his workplace? ",
		answer: "He wrote an angry note for people to stop eating HIS SANDWICH.",
		score: 300,
		catagory: "Pinnacle Events",
		count: 30,
		vidanswer: "<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/6tqmXTYa3Xw?start=0' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>",

	},

	{
		question:"Who is at the door?",
		answer: "Joshua-- Rachel's EX",
		score: 400,
		catagory: "Pinnacle Events",
		count: 59,
		vid:"<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/C5MN7Q3sD8o?start=146&end=173' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>",
		vidanswer:"<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/C5MN7Q3sD8o?start=173&end=211' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>",
	},

	{
		question:"When Joey was in Pyramids, what were his 3 go-to answers when his partner was describing something white?",
		answer: "Paper, Snow, A Ghost",
		score: 500,
		catagory: "Pinnacle Events",
		count: 30,
		vidanswer:"<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/DpRfq7xHstg?start=65&end=97' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>",
	}
];


 vm.questionsQuotes = [

   	{
   		question:"Out of the 6 friends who said: 'How you doin ?' ",
   		answer: "Joey",
   		score: 100,
   		catagory: "Quotes",
   		count: 30
   	},

   	{
   		question:"Out of the 6 Friends who said: 'You're over me? When were you under me?'",
   		answer: "Ross",
   		score: 200,
   		catagory: "Quotes",
   		count: 30,
   	},

   	{
   		question:"Out of the 6 Friends who said:'You know, one of these times you're going to really be naked and we're not gonna come over.' ",
   		answer: "Joey",
   		score: 300,
   		catagory: "Quotes",
   		count: 30,
   	},

   	{
   		question:" Out of the 6 Friends who said: 'Everybody at my school heard it! You were the hermaphrodite cheerleader from Long Island?'",
   		answer: "Chandler",
   		score: 400,
   		catagory: "Quotes",
   		count: 30,
   	},

   	{
   		question:"Out of the 6 Friends who said:'I WAS the pile of coats!!!' ",
   		answer: "Monica",
   		score: 500,
   		catagory: "Quotes",
   		count: 30,
   		vidanswer:"<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/XeE2-VSrEtU?start=73&end=112' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>",
   	}

 ];

 vm.questionsHolidayEp = [
   {
 		question:"Which character accidentally got a turkey stuck on their head at Thanksgiving?",
 		answer: "Joey",
 		score: 100,
 		catagory: "Holiday Episodes",
 		count: 30,
 	},

 	{
 		question:"In the episode where Ross wants Ben to learn about Hanukkah what does Ross dress up like?",
 		answer: "Armadillo",
 		score: 200,
 		catagory: "Holiday Episodes",
 		count: 30
 	},

 	{
 		question:"What does Rachel do next?",
 		answer: "She gives away all the candy",
 		score: 300,
 		catagory: "Holiday Episodes",
 		count: 57,
 		vid:"<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/utiZvi-VBP0?start=51&end=75' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>",
 		vidanswer:"<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/utiZvi-VBP0?start=75&end=95' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>",
 	},

 	{
 		question:"Who guest starred during a Thanksgiving Episode in Friends?",
 		answer: "Brad Pitt",
 		score: 400,
 		catagory: "Holiday Episodes",
 		count:30,
 		vidanswer:"<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/n8OTYXkHwWk?start=51&end=89' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>",
 	},

 	{
 		question:"What's Rachel's confession?",
 		answer: "She wasn't supposed to put beef in the truffle",
 		score: 500,
 		catagory: "Holiday Episodes",
 		count: 81,
 		vid: "<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/X5LPuZrQryc?start=38&end=086' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>",
 		vidanswer: "<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='https://www.youtube.com/embed/X5LPuZrQryc?start=86&end=144' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>",
 	}
];


 vm.questionsRandomQuirks = [
   {
     question:"Who went to a sleep clinic, because of snoring problems?",
     answer: "Joey",
     score: 100,
     catagory: "Random Quirks",
     count: 30
   },

   {
     question:"After the scene what does Ross say next?",
     answer: "DANGER - DANGER!!!",
     score: 200,
     catagory: "Random Quirks",
     count: 50,
     vid: "<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='http://www.youtube.com/embed/0ev_ob4mVwg?autoplay=1&end=020' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>",
     vidanswer: "<div class='col-sm-6' style= 'margin: auto'><div class='embed-responsive embed-responsive-16by9 hidden-xs'><iframe class='embed-responsive-item' src='http://www.youtube.com/embed/0ev_ob4mVwg?start=20&end=035' allowfullscreen></iframe></div></div>",
   },

   {
     question:"What did Monica and Ross call their dance that they performed on Dick Clark's Rockin' New Years Eve?",
     answer: "The Routine",
     score: 300,
     catagory: "Random Quirks",
     count: 30,

   },

   {
     question:"What was going to be Phoebe's fiance's name if she were to change her name to Princess Conseula Banana Hammock?",
     answer: "Crap Bag",
     score: 400,
     catagory: "Random Quirks",
     count: 30,
   },

   {
     question:"Phoebe believed that someone died every time she went where?",
     answer: "The Dentist",
     score: 500,
     catagory: "Random Quirks",
     count: 30,
   }

 ];
}// end of FriendsIndexController
